partnershipcard.co.uk 2012-11-25

# Privacy Policy | partnership card | John Lewis Financial Services

## 

This Privacy Statement sets out our current policies about how your personal and financial information is dealt with and demonstrates our commitment to your privacy. We may change the content or services found on our site at any time without notice, and consequently our privacy policy may change at any time in the future. You agree to revisit this page regularly and your continued access to or use of this site will mean that you agree to any changes.

For essential information about using our website, please read the legal information provided.  

Public areas onsite are those that can be viewed without you having to log into your account. These also exclude the full Special Offers page - which requires you to enter the first 6 digits of your _partnership card_ number to be viewed.

When using the public portion of the site you are not required to provide us with any personal information and we do not monitor or collect any personally identifiable information from you on your use of the public portions of the site. We may track the number of users who visit areas of the site, but this tracking will not identify you.

We may also record the location of your computer on the internet for systems administration and trouble-shooting purposes and to report aggregate information.  

If you provide us with certain up-to-date data about yourself, such as applying for a credit card, we will handle that data in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

We maintain strict security standards and procedures to prevent unauthorised access of your data by anyone, including our staff. We use secure technologies including data encryption, firewalls and server authentication to protect the security of your data. All our Group companies, staff and third parties who provide our support services are required to observe our privacy standards and allow us to audit them for compliance.

John Lewis Financial Services Limited and companies in the John Lewis Partnership will never release your personal details to any company outside the John Lewis Partnership for mailing or marketing purposes.  

Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer's hard drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies can make the internet more useful by storing information about your preferences on particular sites and enabling website owners to provide more useful features to their users. Cookies contain no name or address information or any information that will enable anyone to contact you via telephone, email or any other means.

Most web browsers are initially set to accept cookies but if you prefer you can set your browser to disable cookies or inform you when they are set. However, given that we may sometimes use cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of our website if you disable them.

Our web pages use tracking technology to enable us to count users who have visited certain pages on our website. We do not use tracking data to access your personal information and it is simply a tool we use to analyse which web pages customers' view, in an aggregated manner. If you prefer us not to collect any such information, simply set your browser to disable cookies. Information on how to disable cookies can be obtained by referring to your browser help function, often found in the menu at the top of the screen.  

We sometimes work with third parties to research certain usage and activities on our website on our behalf. No personal information about you is shared, however in the course of conducting this research these third parties may place a unique cookie on your browser.  

If you have any questions regarding privacy issues, please call _partnership card_ services on **0845 300 3833** lines are open 24 hours, 7 days a week. To ensure the accuracy of our conversation and to help us to continually improve our service and in the interest of security, we may monitor and/or record your telephone calls with us.
